Guide to the Northwest Horticultural Council Records 1953-1977
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
- Series 3: Transportation
  - Subseries 3.2: 1975-1976
    - Ocean Rates
      - South American Rate Conference, 54 items. (Box 16, Folder 604)
    - Office of Market Development: Western Region, 26 items. (Box 16, Folder 605)
    - Railroad Correspondence, 28 items. (Box 16, Folder 606)
    - Seaport Export, 1 item. (Box 16, Folder 607)
    - Steamship Schedules, 2 items. (Box 16, Folder 608)
    - Sunkist Complaint Versus Railroad, 1 item. (Box 16, Folder 609)
    - Tolan, Fred H., 15 items. (Box 16, Folder 610)
    - Transcontinental Freight Bureau, 54 items. (Box 16, Folder 611)
    - Transcontinental Freight Bureau, 47 items. (Box 16, Folder 612)
    - Transcontinental Freight Bureau, 61 items. (Box 16, Folder 613)
    - Transcontinental Freight Bureau Applications, 199 items. (Box 16, Folder 614-618)
    - Transportation Committee, 63 items. (Box 16, Folder 619)
    - Transportation Committee, 23 items. (Box 16, Folder 620)
    - Legislation, 45 items. (Box 16, Folder 621)
    - Truck Brokers, 10 items. (Box 16, Folder 622)
    - Trucks and Exempt Carriage, 20 items. (Box 16, Folder 623)
    - United Fresh Fruit and Vegetable Association, 44 items. (Box 16, Folder 624)
    - United Fresh Fruit and Vegetable Association, 36 items. (Box 16, Folder 625)
    - Washington Utilities and Transportation, 2 items. (Box 16, Folder 626)
  - Subseries 3.3.2: 1976-1977
    - Anti-Dumping Duties, 2 items. (Box 17, Folder 627)
    - Ex Parte 256-299 and 303, 45 items. (Box 17, Folder 628)
    - Ex Parte 256-299 and 303, 54 items. (Box 17, Folder 629)
    - Ex Parte 256-299 and 303, 37 items. (Box 17, Folder 630)
    - Ex Parte 301 and 305: Fuel Surcharge, 3 items. (Box 17, Folder 631)
    - Ex Parte 305: Ten Percent Surcharge, 4 items. (Box 17, Folder 632)
    - Ex Parte 310: Seven Percent Rail Increase, 10 items. (Box 17, Folder 633)
    - Ex Parte 313: Five Percent Rail Increase, 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 634)
    - Ex Parte 318: Seven Percent Rail Increase, 2 items. (Box 17, Folder 635)
    - Ex Parte 324: Seasonal, Regional Peak, 43 items. (Box 17, Folder 636)
    - Ex Parte 324: Seasonal, Regional Peak Demand Rates, 2 items. (Box 17, Folder 637)
    - Ex Parte 330: Five Percent Nationwide, 37 items. (Box 17, Folder 638)
    - Ex Parte 331, 17 items. (Box 17, Folder 639)
    - Ex Parte 336: Four Percent Increase, 46 items. (Box 17, Folder 640)
    - Ex Parte 338: Adequate Railroad Revenue Levels, 26 items. (Box 17, Folder 641)
    - Ex Parte 338: Statements, 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 642)
    - Freight Rates: Miscellaneous, 32 items. (Box 17, Folder 643)
    - Highway Users Conference: Washington and National, 4 items. (Box 17, Folder 644)
    - Interstate Commission, Miscellaneous, 47 items. (Box 17, Folder 645)
    - Interstate Commission, Service Orders, 10 items. (Box 17, Folder 646)
    - Motor Carrier: Weights and Miscellaneous, 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 647)
    - National Container Committee, 17 items. (Box 17, Folder 648)
    - National Container Committee, Fruit and Vegetable Claims Committee, 16 items. (Box 17, Folder 649)
    - National Container Committee, Perishable Freight Committee, 5 items. (Box 17, Folder 650)
    - Ocean Rates
      - Pacific European Conference, 110 items. (Box 17, Folder 651-652)
      - Pace Conference, 17 items. (Box 17, Folder 653)
      - Pacific Westbound Conference, 36 items. (Box 17, Folder 654)
      - South-American Latin American Conference, 12 items. (Box 17, Folder 655)
    - Railroad Correspondence, 23 items. (Box 17, Folder 656)
    - Seaport Export, 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 657)
    - Steamship Schedules, 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 658)
    - Texas, 77 items. (Box 17, Folder 659)
    - Transcontinental Freight Bureau Applications
      - Deciduous, 213 items. (Box 17, Folder 660-663)
      - Miscellaneous, 140 items. (Box 17, Folder 664-667)
    - Transportation Committee, 76 items. (Box 17, Folder 668)
    - Transportation Committee Legislation, 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 669)
    - Truck Brokers, 23 items. (Box 17, Folder 670)
    - Trucks and Exempt Carriage, 23 items. (Box 17, Folder 671)
    - United Fresh Fruit and Vegetable Association, Bill of Lading, 36 items. (Box 17, Folder 672)
    - Washington Utilities and Transportation, 30 items. (Box 17, Folder 673)
- Series 4: Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1953-1975
  - Board of Trustees
    - National Horticultural Council, 1973-1974; 44 items. (Box 18, Folder 674)
    - Northwest Horticultural Council, 76 items. (Box 18, Folder 675-676)
  - European Representative
    - 1973-1974, 17 items. (Box 18, Folder 677)
    - 1974-1975, 23 items. (Box 18, Folder 678)
    - Disbursements, 54 items. (Box 18, Folder 679)
  - Export Fruits, 1969-1970; 43 items. (Box 18, Folder 680)
  - Export Fruits, 1969-1970; 29 items. (Box 18, Folder 681)
  - F General Correspondence, 1968-1973; 64 items. (Box 18, Folder 682)
  - Falk, Ernest (Personal), 1973-1974; 45 items. (Box 18, Folder 683)
  - Falk, Ernest (Personal), 1973-1974; 28 items. (Box 18, Folder 684)
  - Filing Index
    - 1972-1973, 4 items. (Box 18, Folder 685)
    - 1973-1974, 4 items. (Box 18, Folder 686)
    - 1974-1975, 4 items. (Box 18, Folder 687)
  - Fruits: Statistics, 1967-1970; 35 items. (Box 18, Folder 688)
  - Northwest Horticultural Council Bulletins, 1970-1971; 38 items. (Box 18, Folder 689)
  - Northwest Horticultural Council Bulletins, 1970-1971; 48 items. (Box 18, Folder 690)
  - Northwest Horticultural Council
    - 1971-1972, 121 items. (Box 18, Folder 691-693)
    - 1972-1973, 128 items. (Box 18, Folder 694-696)
    - 1973-1974, 163 items. (Box 18, Folder 697-700)
    - 1974-1975, 36 items. (Box 18, Folder 701)
  - Report: Survey of European Apple and Pear Production and Marketing, 1973; 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 702)
  - Statements Before Various Committees, 1953-1967, 180 items. (Box 18, Folder 703-705)
  - Traffic Association Trust Fund, 1974-1975; 27 items. (Box 18, Folder 706)
  - Washington State Department of Labor and Industries, 1974-1975; 2 items. (Box 18, Folder 707)
  - Withholding Tax
    - 1973-1974, 6 items. (Box 18, Folder 708)
    - 1974-1975, 23 items. (Box 18, Folder 709)